<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Kinship</string>
    <string name="title_home">Home</string>
    <string name="title_blood_request">Blood Request</string>
    <string name="title_settings">Settings</string>
    <string name="title_activity_home">Home</string>

    <!-- TODO: Remove or change this placeholder text -->
    <string name="blood_donator_instructions_heading">BLOOD DONATOR INSTRUCTIONS</string>
    <string name="blood_donator_instructions_textview">
        <b><font color='#D14035'>Instructions to Blood Donors Before Blood Donation</font></b>\n\n
        1. Take light refreshment/food before 2 hours of blood donation. \n
        2. Women should avoid blood donation during their menstrual bleeding. \n
        3. Person who has consumed alchocol should avoid giving blood for next 24 hours. \n
        4. Person who had recent attack of infection like Jaundice, Typhoid, Malaria, Rubella, etc., should not give blood. \n
        5. Person who had undergone major surgery should avoid blood donation for 6 months. \n
        6. Pregnancy, lactating women should avoid blood donation.\n\n
        <b><font color='#D14035'>Instructions to Blood Donors After Blood Donation</font></b>\n\n
        1. Drink plenty of liquids for the whole day. \n
        2. Eat well and do not remain hungry. \n
        3. Do not smoke for half an hour. \n
        4. Do not do any heavy exercises on that day. \n
        5. Do not do any vehicle for 1-2 hours. \n
        6. Do not participate in sports and games on the day of blood donation. \n
        7. If there is any bleeding from the place from where blood is collected, apply pressure and raise the arm for a few minutes.\n\n
        <b><font color='#D14035'>Instructions to Blood Donors How much blood can be taken in your Body</font></b>\n\n
        1. Our body has 5.5 litre of blood of which only 350 ml - 450 ml of blood is taken depending upon weight of donor. \n
        2. Majority of healthy adults can tolerate withdrawal of one unit of blood. \n
        3. The withdrawan blood volume is restored within 24 hours and the haemoglobin and cell components are restored in 2 months. \n
        4. Therefore it is safe to donate blood every three months.
    </string>
    <string name="blood_requestor_instructions_textview">
        <b><font color='#D14035'>Instructions to Blood Donors Before Blood Donation</font></b>\n\n</string>
    <string name="hello"></string>
    <string name="settingsfragment_cardview1_textview">Edit Profile</string>
    <string name="settingsfragment_cardview2_textview">Notifications</string>
    <string name="settingsfragment_cardview3_textview">Language</string>
    <string name="alert_language_settings_cardView_textView">Language Settings</string>
    <string name="alert_language_settings_cardView_constraintLayout_cancelButton">Cancel</string>
    <string name="alert_language_settings_cardView_constraintLayout_okButton">Ok</string>
</resources>
